真不敢相信你会这么说
I can't believe you would actually say that.
我宁可当花生先生 也不当盐先生
I would much rather be Mr. Peanut than Mr. Salty.
不会吧，盐先生是个水手哦
No way. Mr. Salty is a sailor, all right?
他一定是最强悍的零食
He's gotta be, like, the toughest snack there is.
难说，不要惹到玉米坚果
I don't know. You don't wanna mess with corn nuts.
他们是疯子
They're crazy.
我的天，我的天 你们快过来看
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. You gotta come see this.
有一个恶心的人拿着望远镜
There's some creep out there with a telescope.
真不敢相信 他居然直接向我们这边看
I can't believe it. He's looking right at us.
真是有病
Oh, that is so sick.
我有被强奸的感觉
I feel violated.
而且是不太好的那种
And not in a good way.
为什么有人能这么做
How can people do that?
你们看，丑胖子买了一双倒立鞋
Oh, you guys, look. Ugly Naked Guy got gravity boots.
《老友记》 第一季 第20集：邪恶的矫正牙医
Friends S01E20: The One with the Evil Orthodontist
（主演：詹妮弗·安妮斯顿）
（主演：柯特妮·考克斯）
（主演：丽莎·库卓）
（主演：马特·勒布朗）
（主演：马修·派瑞）
（主演：大卫·修蒙）
（中央咖啡厅）
我告诉你们 多年后，小学生都会把这个…
I'm telling you, years from now, school children will study it...
当作史上最棒的第一次约会来研究
...as one of the greatest first dates of all time.
顺利到不可思议
It was unbelievable.
我们非常的自在 不需要耍心机
We could totally be ourselves. We didn't have to play any games.
- 你打电话给她了吗  - 让她知道我喜欢她 你疯了吗
- So have you called her yet? - Let her know I like her? Are you insane?
（制片：塔德·史帝文斯）
你们男生真差劲
Guys. It's gross.
才过一天而已 你要我看起来很黏人吗
It's the next day. How needy do I wanna seem?
（编剧：多提·阿布朗）
我说的对  对吧
I'm right. Right?
- 吊她胃口 - 是，绝对的
- Let her dangle. - Yeah, definitely.
哦
Oh.
真不敢相信我爸妈 给我压力…
I can't believe my parents are pressuring me...
要我找你们这种人
...to find one of you people.
天啊，直接打个电话吧
God. Come on. Just do it.
打给她 别摆出一付臭男人的样子
Call her. Stop being so testosterone-y.
对了，旧金山真有这道菜
Which, by the way, is the real San Francisco treat.
（导演：彼得邦纳兹）
- 是机器  - 她的答录机
- I got her machine. - Her answering machine?
不 真有意思 是落叶机清扫机。
No, interestingly enough, her leaf blower picked up.
那你怎么不留话
So, um, why didn't you say anything?
不，不，不 上次我毫无准备就留言…
Oh, no, no, no. Last time I left a spontaneous message...
结果讲出〝对，的确〞这种蠢话
...I ended up using the phrase, "Yes, indeed-io."
你们看，是瑞秋和巴瑞 大家不要一起回头看
MONICA: Look, it's Rachel and Barry. No, no, don't everybody look at once.
- 好啦好啦，是怎么回事  - 他们在讲话
- Okay, okay. What's going on? - Okay, they're just talking.
她看起来有没有很生气
Yeah, well, does he look upset?
他看起来是不是 被狠揍过一顿
Does he look like he was just told to shove anything?
没有，他在微笑
No. No, actually, he's smiling.
天啊，不要那样
Oh, my God. Don't do that.
怎么了 怎么了 怎么了
What? What? What?
对面有个男人踢了鸽子一脚
That man across the street just kicked that pigeon.
哦
Oh.
基本上，提案就是这样成为法案的
And basically, that's how a bill becomes a law.
哦
GROUP: Oh.
- 知道了吗  嘿 瑞秋  - 嘿
- See? Hey, Rach. - Hey.
你们还好吧
How'd it go?
说真的，感觉还真好
You know, it was, uh... It was actually really great.
他带我去俄国茶坊吃午餐
Took me to lunch at the Russian Tea Room.
我吃的鸡肉，一碰就有奶油流出来
I had that chicken, you know, where you poke it and butter squirts out.
鸟类今天很衰
Not a good day for birds.
然后我们去逛百货公司
And then we took a walk to Bendel's.
我叫他不要买 但他还是买给我一小瓶香奈儿香水
And I told him not to, but he got me a little bottle of Chanel.
很好，那是你在跟他说…
That's nice. Now was that before or after you told him...
别再打电话 送花  不要再烦你之前还是之后
...to stop calling, stop sending you flowers and to generally leave you alone, huh?
嗯，那个我们一直没提到
Right. Well, we never actually got to that.
再跟他出去 感觉真好 你们知道吗 感觉…
Oh, it was just so nice to see him again, you know? It was...
就是很舒服 熟悉
It was comfortable and it was familiar.
感觉真好
It was just nice.
感觉真好两次了
That's "nice" twice.
瑞秋，这到底是怎么回事？
Rachel, what's going on?
他不是同样那个 被你逃婚的巴瑞吗？
Isn't this the same Barry who you left at the altar?
你都跑去哪里了
Duh. Where have you been?
是啊，可是他今天不一样
Yeah, but it was different with him today.
他今天不是那个讨人厌的牙医
He wasn't, like, Orthodontist Guy, you know?
我们很愉快  这有什么不对吗
I mean, we had fun. Is there anything wrong with that?
有
Yes.
- 为什么  - 我有我的理由
- Why? - I have my reasons.
他其实已经订婚了 而未婚妻刚好是…
Okay, how about the fact that he's engaged to another woman...
你以前的知己呢  这没关系吗
...who just happens to be your ex-best friend?
好啦，好啦，好啦，好啦 我知道这样做很蠢
All right. All right, all right, all right. I know it's stupid.
我今天下午去看他 然后结束这整件事
I'll go see him this afternoon and I will just put an end to it.
哇
Wow.
- 哇 - 哈哈
- Wow. - Ha, ha.
对啊
Yeah.
我没疯吧  以前都不是这样的
I'm not crazy, right? I mean, it was never like that.
你没疯，以前不是这样的
No, it wasn't.
这里有个小水槽真好
Oh. It was so nice having this little sink here.
〝丹妮儿 我没想到答录机会接起来
"Oh, Danielle, I wasn't expecting the machine.
有空的话，打电话给我〞
Give me a call when you get a chance."
再见
Bye-bye.
天啊
Oh, God.
练习两个小时  只说得出这样
That's what you've been working on for the past two hours?
喂，我一直在修改好吗
Hey, I've been honing.
为什么要有盘子声？
What was with the dishes?
我要她以为我在餐厅里…
Oh, uh, I wanted her to think I might be in a restaurant...
我也有自己的娱乐生活
...you know, I might have some kind of life.
总不能让她觉得 我已经练习了两个小时吧
Like I haven't been sitting around here honing for the last two hours?
又来了，那个望远镜男
He's doing it again. The guy with the telescope.
我的天啊
PHOEBE: Oh, my God.
走开，不要再看这边了！
Oh. Go away. Stop looking in here!
好极了，现在他也在跟我们挥手
Great. Now he's waving back.
我们要想办法对付那男的
We gotta do something about that guy.
今天早上 他在窥探我们家，被我抓到
This morning, I caught him looking into our apartment.
我吓一跳 现在好像什么都不能做了
It creeps me out. I feel like I can't do stuff.
你都做些什么？
What kind of stuff?
成熟一点好不好？ 我说得不是什么性感的事…
Will you grow up? I'm not talking about sexy stuff...
我只不过是煮饭时全裸而已
...but, like, when I'm cooking naked.
你煮饭时全裸？
You cook naked?
对啊，吐司、麦片粥 不会溅出来的食物
Yeah, toast, oatmeal. Nothing that spatters.
你们看我干嘛？我又不知道
What are you looking at me for? I didn't know that.
怎么了？
What's the matter?
我只是… 巴瑞，这样不好
Oh, I just... Oh, Barry, this was not good.
不，那感觉非常非常好
No, it was. It was very, very good.
- 那敏蒂呢？ - 比跟敏蒂好太多了
- What about Mindy? - Oh, way better than Mindy.
不是，我是说 你跟敏蒂怎么办？
No, not that. I mean, what about you and Mindy?
如果你愿意，我去跟她退婚
Oh. If you want, I'll just break it off with her.
不，不，不，不
No. No, no, no.
不，不要那样 不要因为我退婚
No, don't do that. Not for me.
法柏医生，巴比洛许 已经来调整牙套
BERNICE: Dr. Farber, Bobby Rush is here for his adjustment.
谢谢你，柏妮丝
Thanks, Bernice.
我们这个周末去远一点的地方吧
Let's go away this weekend.
巴瑞，拜托，这太…
Oh, Barry. Come on. This is all way too...
不，我们可以去阿鲁巴岛
No, we can go to Aruba.
当我去那里 本来是我们蜜月要去的地方…
When I went there on what would've been our honeymoon...
那里真的很美，你会很喜欢的
...it was, uh... It was really nice. You would've liked it.
我的胸罩呢？
I had a bra.
法柏医生
Hey, Dr. Farber.
好，葛林小姐 一切看起来都很好
All right, Miss Green, everything looks fine.
我想我们已经看到一点进展了
Yep, I think we're starting to see some real progress here.
- 怎么？ - 我12岁，不代表我很笨
- What? - I'm 12, I'm not stupid.
- 我能不能借用你们的电话？ - 好
- Can I use your phone? - Yeah.
不过，谨作为参考…
Uh, but for future reference, um, that thing in your hand...
你手上那个也可以当电话用
...can also be used as a phone.
好，线路没问题
Yes, it's working.
她为什么不回电？
Why isn't she calling me back?
她也许根本没听到你的留言
Maybe she never got your message.
你也可以打她的答录机 如果“哔”很多声的话…
You know, you could call her machine, and if she has a lot of beeps...
表示她还没听留官
...that means she probably didn't get her messages yet.
- 你们不觉得这样很… - 着急？黏人？可悲？
- You don't think that makes me seem...? - Desperate? Needy? Pathetic?
你一定看过我的征友启示
Ah, you obviously saw my personal ad.
- 哔了几声  - 她接起来了
- How many beeps? - She answered.
那时候我们先前讨论过的〝喂〞 就很好用
You see, this is where you'd use that "hello" word we talked about.
我才不要 她已经听过我的留言…
I'm not going to. She obviously got my message...
选择不回我电话 现在我不但黏人 还被冷落
...and is choosing not to call me. Now I'm needy and snubbed.
天啊 真想念单纯 只是黏人的感觉
God, I miss just being needy.
- 嘿  - 嘿
GROUP: Hey.
他的反应如何
So how'd he take it?
其实还蛮不错的
Pretty well, actually.
瑞秋 你的头发上 怎么会有牙线
Uh, Rach. How come you have dental floss in your hair?
是吗
Oh, do I?
我们在牙医椅上做爱
We ended up having sex in his chair.
你们在牙医椅上做爱
You had sex in his chair?
我说得有点大声 对不对
I said that a little too loudly, didn't I?
你们什么
You had what?
在牙医椅上做爱
Sex in his chair.
怎么…
What?
你在想什么？
What were you thinking?
我也不知道  我们都还对对方有感觉
I don't know. I mean, we still care about each other.
我们有一段过去 就跟你和卡萝一样
There's a history there. It's like you and Carol.
不，不，不
No. No, no.
跟我和卡萝完全不同
It's nothing like me and Carol.
拜托，如果她跟你说 〝罗斯，我现在就要你…
Please. If she said to you, "Ross, I want you on this couch...
在这沙发上，立刻〞 你会怎么说？
...right here, right now," what would you say?
如果有帮助的话，我会坐过来
If it helps I could slide over.
那完全是两回事
It's a totally different situation.
苹果跟柳橙 矫正牙医和女同志…
It's apples and oranges. It's orthodontists and lesbians...
我要走了
I gotta go.
- 你要去哪里  - 我就是得走，可以吗
- Where are you going? - I just have to go, all right?
我走还需要理由吗  我的人生还有别的事要做
Do I need a reason, huh? I have things to do with my life.
我的行程排得非常紧
I have a jam-packed schedule.
我已经赶得喘不过气来了 可以吗
And I am late for keeping up with it, okay?
喂  喂
Hello? Hello?
喂
Hello?
敏蒂
Huh. Mindy.
嘿，你好
Hi. Hey, how are you?
对，我听说了 恭喜，这真是太好了
Yes, yes, I heard. Congratulations. That is so great.
真的，噢，天啊…
Really, oh, God...
好
Okay.
好，我明天要上班…
Okay, I'm working tomorrow...
但是如果你愿意 可以过来看看
...but if you want, you can come by if you'd like.
好
Okay.
太好了
Great.
好
All right.
明天见
So I'll see you tomorrow.
再见 好
Okay. Bye.
噢，天啊，噢，天啊，噢，天啊
Oh, God. Oh, God. Oh, God.
敏蒂还好吗
So how's Mindy?
她明天想来看我
Oh, she wants to see me tomorrow.
她的语气听起来很怪 我得打电话给巴瑞
Oh, she sounded really weird. I gotta call Barry.
喂，是我，我才…敏蒂
Hi, it's me. I just... Ha! Mindy.
敏蒂，嘿
Mindy. Hi.
不，我想你应该在那里
No, I figured that's where you'd be.
地狱里充满了你这种人
Hell is filled with people like you.
又来了，偷窥狂又来了
He's back. The peeper's back.
- 蹲下  - 蹲下
- Get down. - Get down?
你变成鬼了
And boogie.
谢谢，我得去上班 顺便让敏蒂把我的眼睛挖出来
Thanks, but I gotta go to work and get my eyes scratched out by Mindy.
放心，她也许根本不知道
Relax. She may not even know.
拜托，我七个月没跟她连络 她突然打电话给我
Please, I haven't heard from her in seven months, and now she calls me.
还会为了什么事
I mean, what else is it about?
她曾经是我最好的朋友
She was my best friend, you guys.
我们一起去夏令营…
We went to camp together...
- 她教我如何接吻…  - 是吗
...she taught me how to kiss... - Yeah?
现在，我成了第三者
Now, you know, I'm, like, the other woman.
- 我觉得好… - 有情趣
- Ugh, I feel so... - Naughty.
- 晚点见 - 我送你出去
- I'll see you guys later. - I'll walk out with you.
她教你接吻的时候 你们在夏令营…
When she taught you to kiss, you were at camp...
穿的是小件紧身制服 还是…
...and were you wearing any kind of little uniform or...?
算了
That's fine, yeah.
好，我要去上厕所 你能不能帮我看着电话
Okay, I'm gonna go the bathroom. Will you watch my phone?
- 你为什么不把电话拿进去  - 嘿
- Why don't you just take it with you? - Hey.
我们还没进展到第二次约会 她需要听我嘘嘘吗
We haven't been on a second date. She needs to hear me pee?
你为什么不干脆打给她
Why don't you just call her?
我不能打给她，我已经留言了 我也是有尊严的
I can't call her. I left a message. I have some pride.
- 是吗  - 不是
- Do you? - No.
丹妮儿，你好
Danielle, hi.
我是钱德
Hi, it's Chandler.
我很好
I'm fine. Ahem.
是这样的…
Uh, listen...
不知道你有没有打电话给我 因为我很白痴…
I don't know if you tried to call me because, uh, idiot that I am...
不小心把电话关掉
...I accidentally shut off my phone.
哦，好，没问题 好极了，好
Ahem. Oh, okay. That's fine. That's great. Okay.
她在另一线上讲电话 她再打回来
She's on the other line. She's gonna call me back.
She's on the other line, gonna call me back.
- 你不是想去嘘嘘  - 所以我才跳来跳去
- Don't you have to pee? - That's why I'm dancing.
- 敏蒂 - 嘿，你好
- Mindy. - Hey, you.
嘿，你好
Hey, you.
最近还好吗
So, what's up?
我们应该坐下来说
Um, we should really be sitting for this.
唔
Hmm.
我们当然要坐下
Sure we should.
- 嗯… - 我知道最近事情不太对
- So... - Now, I know things have been weird lately.
但是你是我认识最久的老朋友 除了萝莉·莎菲…
But you're my oldest friend, except for Laurie Schaefer...
我现在不跟她说话了…
...who I don't talk to anymore...
自从减肥后 她就一副全世界都欠她的样子…
...because she's bitter that she lost the weight...
而且，她的脸居然还不是很漂亮
...and it turns out, she doesn't have a pretty face.
好，我只问你一次 而且我要很诚实的答案
Okay, I'm gonna just ask you this once, and I want a straight answer.
好
Okay.
你愿不愿意当我的伴娘？
Will you be my maid of honor?
- 当然罗！ - 那就太好了！
- Of course! - Oh, that's so great!
太好了！太好了！
It is! It is!
- 你就只想问这件事吗  - 对啊
- Is that all you wanted to ask? - That's all.
怎么了 怎么了
What? What?
不只这件事
That's not all.
- 一定只有这件事   - 不，不止
- Oh, sure it is. - Oh, no, it isn't. No.
我觉得巴瑞在跟别人约会
I think Barry's seeing someone in the city.
你怎么会有这种想法
What would make you think that?
自从我们宣布订婚后 他就怪怪的
Well, ever since we announced the engagement, he's acted weird.
昨晚他回家的时候 身上有香奈儿的香水味
And then last night, he came home smelling like Chanel.
真的吗
Really?
敏蒂，如果这样讲 你会好过一点…
Mindy, if it'll make you feel any better...
巴瑞跟我订婚后 他的行为也很诡异
...when Barry and I got engaged, he went through a weird thing too.
噢，天啊 我就是怕这一点
Oh, God. You see, that's what I was afraid of.
- 什么 你就是怕哪一点  - 好吧，好吧
- What? What's what you were afraid of? - Okay, okay.
巴瑞跟你订婚后，他跟我…
When Barry was engaged to you, he and I...
也发展出一点什么
...kind of had a little thing on the side.
- 什么  - 我知道，我知道
- What? - I know, I know.
他跟我求婚时 大家都告诉我〝不要接受
When he proposed to me, everyone said, "Don't do it.
他那样对待瑞秋，对你也会那样〞 现在我自己觉得好傻
He's gonna do to you what he did to Rachel." And now I feel so stupid.
哈哈
Ha, ha.
噢，敏蒂
Hmm. Oh, Mindy.
噢，你真的好傻
Oh, you are so stupid.
噢，我们真的都好傻
Oh, we are both so stupid.
什么意思
What do you mean?
- 很熟悉的味道吧  - 噢，不会吧
- Smell familiar? MINDY: Oh, no.
嗯哼
RACHEL: Mm-hm.
我很抱歉
Oh, I'm so sorry.
噢，不，是我很抱歉
Oh, no, me. I am so sorry.
不，是我很抱歉，对不起
No, I am sorry. I'm sorry.
老天
Oh, my.
四个字母，〝发出声音〞
Four letters, "circle or hoop."
响啊，该死，响啊
Ring, damn it, ring.
谢谢
Thanks.
你知道我们的电话坏掉了吗
You know our phone's not working?
什么
What?
我从咖啡厅打电话给你 一直没有人接
I tried to call you from the coffee shop. There was no answer.
我把电话关掉了
I turned it off.
我的天啊，我把电话关掉
Mother of God, I turned it off.
就像你跟她讲的那样
Just like you told her you did.
我只是指出反讽之处
Just pointing out the irony.
我去跟对面的门房谈过
So listen, I went across the street and talked to the doorman.
知道偷窥狂的名字 电话可以用了吧
I got the peeper's name. Can I use the phone?
能不能借用你的电话？
Can I use your phone?
对，请给我 辛尼·马克斯的电话号码
Yeah, the number for a Sidney Marks, please.
〝加温的工具〞
"Heating device."
电热器
Radiator.
两个字
Five letters.
〝电器〞
"Rdtor."
辛尼在吗
Yeah, is Sidney there?
哦，你就是
Oh, this is?
- 辛尼是个女人 - 辛尼是个女人，那又怎样
- Sidney's a woman. - So she's a woman, so what?
对，对，那又怎样
Yeah, yeah, so what?
我住在你对面…
Look, I live across the street...
我知道你喜欢用望远镜偷窥
...and I know all about you and your telescope.
我很不高兴，知道吗
And I don't appreciate it, okay?
对，我现在就可以看到你，喂
Yeah, I can see you right now. Hello?
如果我喜欢穿着内裤 在我家跑来跑去…
Look, if I wanna walk around my apartment in my underwear...
我没有必要觉得…谢谢
...I shouldn't have to feel like... Thank you.
那不是重点
That's not really the point.
重点是…
The point is, that...
- 主要是重量训练，但是偶尔… - 乔伊
- Mostly free-weights, but occasionally... - Joey.
对 我的邻居 揭发的
Yeah, my neighbor. Yeah, the brunette.
她说你那天 穿那件绿洋装的时候很漂亮
She said you looked pretty that day in the green dress.
绿洋装  真的吗
The green dress? Really?
她说那天你很像英格丽褒曼
She said you looked like Ingrid Bergman that day.
哪有
Heh. No.
- 嘿 - 嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
- 有空吗  - 当然，当然
- You got a second? - Sure, sure.
请…
Come on...
…进
...in.
你好，亲爱的
Hello, sweetheart.
- 你们两个在这里干嘛  - 我们来甩你
- What you guys doing here? - Uh, we are here to break up with you.
你们一起
Both of you?
我们觉得你是个大烂人 你应该要很衰
We think you're a horrible human being, and bad things should happen to you.
对不起 对不起 天啊 真对不起
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. God, I am so sorry.
我是大白痴，我很软弱 无法控制自己
I'm an idiot. I was weak. I couldn't help myself.
不管我做了什么，我会那么做 都是因为我那么爱你
Whatever I did, I only did because I love you so much.
你是在跟哪一个讲，巴瑞
Uh, which one of us are you talking to there, Bar?
唔
Um...
敏蒂
Mindy.
敏蒂，当然是敏蒂 一直都是敏蒂
Mindy, of course, Mindy. It was always Mindy.
甚至包括我们 在那张椅子上做爱的时候
Even when we were having sex in that chair?
我发誓，不管我在做什么 心里想的都是你
I swear, look, whatever I was doing, I was always thinking of you.
拜托哦
Oh, please.
第二次的时候，就算 排队等你挑，你都会认不出她来
During that second time, you couldn't have picked her out of a lineup.
你们还做了两次
You did it twice?
第一次不能算数 你也认识巴瑞
Well, the first time didn't really count. You know, it was Barry.
噢，对哦
Oh, right.
甜心，宝贝，亲爱的…
Honey, baby, sweetheart, look...
再给我一次机会，好不好
Just give me another chance, okay?
我们再重新来过 我们回去阿鲁巴岛
We'll start all over again. We'll go back to Aruba.
你怎么说
What do you say?
法柏医生，有点紧急状况 需要你处理
BERNICE [OVER INTERCOM]: Dr. Farber, we've got an emergency here.
杰森卡斯达拉诺 被活动牙套呛到
Jason Castalano's choking on his retainer.
天啊，我马上过去，柏妮丝
Oh, God. Uh, I'll be right there, Bernice.
真的，请不要离开，好吗
Look, please, please don't go anywhere, okay?
- 我马上回来 - 好
- I'll be right back. - Okay.
好，我们会留在这里 继续恨你
Okay, and we'll be here, hating you.
有没有看到 他走出去的时候 满身大汗
See how he was sweating when he walked out of here?
我抓他的下面 你就可以踢他…
If I'm hogging the ball, you jump right in there...
然后揍他两拳 我告诉你 那会感觉超爽
...and take a couple of punches. Because I'm telling you, this feels great.
嗯，我很确定我还是会嫁他
Yeah, I'm pretty sure I'm still gonna marry him.
你在说什么啊
What are you talking about?
敏蒂，那家伙是个恶魔
Mindy, the guy is the devil.
他是披着人皮的撒旦
He is Satan in a smock.
说真的，我知道他不完美
Look, I know he's not perfect.
但是，到头来 我还是…
But the truth is, at the end of the day...
我还是想当…
...I still really wanna be...
巴瑞·法柏牙医…
...Mrs. Dr. Barry Farber...
医师娘
...D.D.S.
噢，天啊
Oh, God.
我希望你还是能够为我高兴
I hope you can find some way to be happy for me.
也希望你仍然愿意当我的伴娘
And I hope you'll still be my maid of honor.
我希望巴瑞不会在阿鲁巴岛 把你生吞活剥吃掉
And I hope Barry doesn't kill you and eat you in Aruba.
你还好吗
You okay?
还好
Yeah.
真的
Really?
Yeah.
你知道吗，我把巴瑞丢在婚礼上，逃了婚后…
You know, ever since I ran out on Barry at the wedding...
我想过我的决定是否正确
...I have wondered whether I made the right choice.
现在我知道了
Oh. And now I know.
很为你高兴
MONICA: I'm so glad.
大日子呦
Big day.
好，我可以赞成 花生先生比较会穿衣服
All right, I'll give you this: Mr. Peanut is a better dresser.
他戴着单片眼镜，加上礼帽…
I mean, he's got the monocle, he's got the top hat...
你们知道他是同志吗
Did you know he's gay?
只是想澄清一下 你在揪花生先生出柜吗
I just wanna clarify this. Are you outing Mr. Peanut?
- 钱德  - 丹妮儿，你好
- Chandler? - Danielle, hi.
各位，这位是丹妮儿 丹妮儿，这都是我朋友
Everybody, this is Danielle. Danielle, everybody.
- 你好 - 你好
GROUP: Hi.
- 你怎么会在这里？ - 我一直打电话给你…
- What are you doing here? - I've been calling you...
后来才知道电话号码错了
...but it turns out I had your number wrong.
我从查号台拿到正确号码后 却没人接
And when I finally got the right one from Information, there was no answer.
我就想来这里 看看你好不好
So I thought I'd just come down here and make sure you were okay.
噢，我很好
Oh, uh, I'm okay.
改天我们出去逛逛好吗
Listen, uh, maybe we could get together later?
好啊，我再打给你 还是你打给我，都可以
That sounds good. I'll call you. Or you call me, whatever.
你也知道
- You know. - Ha, ha.
- 当然 - 好
- You got it. CHANDLER: Okay.
- 大伙儿再见 - 再见
- Bye, everybody. GROUP: Bye.
好啊，就是要这样
Woo-hoo! Yeah, there you go.
第二次约会
Second date.
我不确定
I don't know.
你不确定
RACHEL: You don't know?
她看起来很讨人喜欢 但是大老远跑来这里…
Oh, she seems nice, but that thing about her coming all the way here...
只为了看我好不好 有人那么黏人的吗
...just to see if I was okay? I mean, how needy is that?